<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SQL on Mark Marquez</title>
    <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/techs/sql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SQL on Mark Marquez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Mark Marquez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/techs/sql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VC Funding Scrap and Store</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/vc-scraping-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/vc-scraping-project/</guid>
      <description>VC Funding Scrap and Store Overall Project Goals Analyzing data on new funding rounds and venture-funded companies, helping teams maximize the ROI of their new innovations / markets by:
 Collecting data on venture funding rounds and the venture-funded companies. Cleaning/formatting the collected data and sorting it by funding date and time. Storing information into various datatypes such as excel, csv and SQL.  Abstract With data that is sourced from the website &amp;lsquo;VCNewsDaily&amp;rsquo;, this project collects information on new venture funding rounds, along with the details on the funding round and the venture-funded companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPMG Virtual Internship - Bike Shop Marketing ROI</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/kpmg-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/kpmg-project/</guid>
      <description>Using CRM Data to Identify Ideal Customer Profiles and Predict New Sales Abstract: Through a dataset provided by KPMG, an Australian bicycle shop owner was looking to maximize their marketing ROI by analyzing data on their customers and transactions for the past 3 years. This was accomplished by developing customer profiles based on data, along with predicting new sales that referenced data on previous transactions and customer demographics. Results provided a data-driven ideal customer profile, along with a baseline predictive model for customers that have been in the CRM for longer than 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>