<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PORTFOLIO on Mark Marquez</title>
    <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PORTFOLIO on Mark Marquez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Mark Marquez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>From Chaos to Digital Transformation: My Journey with Phoenix Management Solutions</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/it-phoenixmgt-exp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/it-phoenixmgt-exp/</guid>
      <description>From Chaos to Digital Transformation: My Journey with Phoenix Management Solutions Introduction When I first joined Phoenix Management Solutions, the environment could only be described as chaotic. The company, a U.S.-based business process outsourcing firm supporting eight different trucking companies with 25 offices across the nation, was grappling with the immense challenge of scaling its IT infrastructure to meet the demands of rapid growth. The need for streamlined operations and robust systems was urgent, but the path to achieving this was fraught with obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VC Funding Scrap and Store</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/vc-scraping-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/vc-scraping-project/</guid>
      <description>VC Funding Scrap and Store Overall Project Goals Analyzing data on new funding rounds and venture-funded companies, helping teams maximize the ROI of their new innovations / markets by:
 Collecting data on venture funding rounds and the venture-funded companies. Cleaning/formatting the collected data and sorting it by funding date and time. Storing information into various datatypes such as excel, csv and SQL.  Abstract With data that is sourced from the website &amp;lsquo;VCNewsDaily&amp;rsquo;, this project collects information on new venture funding rounds, along with the details on the funding round and the venture-funded companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Price Predictor - Kaggle Build</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/kaggle-real-estate-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/kaggle-real-estate-project/</guid>
      <description>Real Estate Price Predictor - Kaggle Rebuild Project Goals Analyzing data on historical real estate sales to help a potential buyer find undervalued properties by:
 Analyzing and exploring how the general real estate market is broken down (i.e., price, square feet, stories) Analyze how different house features effect sale prices for houses Predict the price of sale of a house based on features and location  Abstract Through a dataset provided by Kaggle for a data science competition, this project analyzes real estate data in the Boston market to help a potential home buyer maximize the ROI of their new home purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPMG Virtual Internship - Bike Shop Marketing ROI</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/kpmg-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/kpmg-project/</guid>
      <description>Using CRM Data to Identify Ideal Customer Profiles and Predict New Sales Abstract: Through a dataset provided by KPMG, an Australian bicycle shop owner was looking to maximize their marketing ROI by analyzing data on their customers and transactions for the past 3 years. This was accomplished by developing customer profiles based on data, along with predicting new sales that referenced data on previous transactions and customer demographics. Results provided a data-driven ideal customer profile, along with a baseline predictive model for customers that have been in the CRM for longer than 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA County Sociodemographic Clustering - Coursera Capstone</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/la-county-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/la-county-project/</guid>
      <description>Project Summary Through a dataset provided by the US government, cities in LA County will be grouped into clusters based on sociodemographic scores to develop benchmarks for each cluster. This will help city officials identify what are the biggest areas for improvement based on cluster (i.e., mental health to upper-class vs school quality to lower-class). Along with mapping out LA County based on socioeconomic clusters to help identify potential visual patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Journey into Data Science and IT During the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/it-ds-pandemic-exp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkAndrewMarquez.com/portfolio/it-ds-pandemic-exp/</guid>
      <description>My Journey into Data Science and IT During the COVID-19 Pandemic Introduction: An Unexpected Turn In the wake of my unexpected layoff in February 2020, just days after my birthday and as the world teetered on the brink of lockdown, I embarked on an unforeseen and transformative journey through the realms of Information Technology (IT) and Data Science.
The Shift to Technology My academic foundation in Cognitive Sciences and experience in brain imaging research and MatLab programming had initially pointed me towards a scientific career.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>